Speaker 1: Thank you, Madam Chair, and I'll submit other questions for the record, but I need to ask your agencies a question for the record relevant to a matter that has taken a lot of our time. For each of you, just go right down the row. Do you believe that it would be appropriate for your agency to secretly search Senate files without seeking
Speaker 2: an external authorization or approval? Just go down the row. Mr. Legend?
Speaker 3: No, sir.
Speaker 2: Ms.
Sullivan?
No, sir, if I
Speaker 4: understand your question, by definition, we are not permitted to conduct a search that is not properly authorized in
some
Speaker 5: fashion. Right
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): answer. The only thing I would limit it is that because my agency involves the attorney general, not every approval would have to be external, but you would have to have the appropriate legal approvals in every instance. Correct. So we'd have to have the appropriate legal.
Speaker 7: Thank you very much, Madam Chair.